A Guide to the Nelson A. Rockefeller Gubernatorial records, Speeches, Series 33 FA372
Rockefeller Archive Center
- 1964 Primary Campaign - New Hampshire, March 6, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1087)
  Hampton, New Hampshire address.
- Primary Campaign 1964 - New Hampshire, March 5, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1088)
  Rochester, New Hampshire - Address and Q&A Transcript.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - New Hampshire, March 6, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1089)
  Camdia, New Hampshire - Transcript of address.
- New Hampshire [Primary Campaign 1964], New Hampshire, March 6, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1090)
  Hudson, New Hampshire - address and Q&A session.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Manchester, New Hampshire, March 9, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1091)
  TV interview, NBC News by Merrill Mueller Pre-primary TV program, WMUR-TV
- 1964 Primary Campaign - California, March 11, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1092)
  Concord, California Chamber of Commerce dinner.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - University of California at Berkeley - Berkeley, California, March 12, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1093)
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Los Angeles, California, March 13, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1094)
  University of Southern California, Los Angeles brunch reception with Board of Trustees and Faculty; College Young Republicans Club.
- Legislative Correspondents Association - Albany, New York, March 14, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1095)
- Primary Campaign 1964 - California Republican Assembly - Fresno, California, March 14, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1096)
  Convention.
- Primary Campaign 1964 - California, March 11, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1097)
  Sacramento; press releases; itinerary for March 11-14.
- Department of Public Works Laboratory Inspection - Albany, New York, March 16, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1098)
- Capital Hill Club - Washington, DC, March 18, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1099)
- Not Used (Box 26, Folder 1100)
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Oregon, March 30, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1101)
  Rally at Bend Community College - Bend, Oregon.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Oregon, March 30, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1102)
  Ontario, Oregon Chamber of Commerce.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Oregon, March 31, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1103)
  Eugene, Oregon Rotary Club.
- Associated Students' Political Union Board - Stanford University - Palo Alto, California, April 1, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1104)
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Los Angeles, California, April 2, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1105)
  Reception and Press Conference - International Hotel University of California Los Angeles - speak to students, press release, transcript
- Detroit Press Club - Detroit, Michigan, April 6, 1964 (Box 26, Folder 1106)
  Detroit Press Club Celebrity Luncheon.
- Primary Campaign 1964 - Detroit, Michigan, April 6, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1107)
  Detroit Press Club; schedule.
- Primary Campaign 1964 - Johns Hopkins University - Baltimore, Maryland, April 8, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1108)
  All-University Convocation.
- Primary Campaign 1964 - Republican Women's Conference - Washington, DC, April 9, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1109)
- Primary Campaign 1964 - Washington, DC, April 9, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1110)
  Luncheon and speech at Women's National Press Club.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Oregon, April 17, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1111)
  Oregon State University convocation - Corvallis, Oregon.
- Gresham Chamber of Commerce - Gresham, Oregon, April 17, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1112)
- City Club of Portland - Portland, Oregon, April 17, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1113)
- Statement on Social Security, April 19, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1114)
- Dedication of Vatican Pavilion - World's Fair - New York City - Cancelled, April 19, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1115)
- Kiwanis Club of San Diego - Luncheon - San Diego, California, April 20, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1116)
- Primary Campaign 1964 - New Orleans, Louisiana, April 21, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1117)
  Pan American Press Seminar and Luncheon.
- World's Fair 1964 - Opening Day Ceremonies - New York City, April 22, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1118)
- World's Fair 1964 - New York State Day - New York City, April 23, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1119)
- Lincoln Center for the Performing Arts - Opening of the New York State Theater - New York City, April 23, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1120)
- Primary Campaign 1964 - Oregon, April 27, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1121)
  Grants Pass, Oregon - Statement on Vietnam.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Sacramento, California, April 28, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1122)
  Luncheon with Sacramento Press Association and California Newspaper Publishers Association.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Los Angeles, California, April 29, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1123)
  Luncheon with Republican Associates.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - West Virginia, April 30, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1124)
  Luncheon in Beckeley, West Virginia.
- California - Miscellaneous Drafts, etc., May 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1125)
- 1964 Primary Campaign - West Virginia, May 1, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1126)
  Law Day ceremony - Morgantown, West Virginia.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - West Virginia, May 1, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1127)
  "Making of the President" Forum - Bethany College - Bethany, West Virginia.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Charleston, West Virginia, April 30, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1128)
  Press Club; transcript; schedules, background materials.
- New York Republican State Committee - New York City, May 6, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1129)
- New York Republican State Committee - New York City, May 6, 1964 (Box 27, Folder 1130)
- Primary Campaign 1964 - Chicago, Illinois, May 7, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1131)
  Luncheon at Executive Club.
- McArthur Court - University of Oregon - Eugene, Oregon, May 8, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1132)
- Primary Campaign 1964 - Oregon, May 8, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1133)
  Campaign Breakfast and Statement - Astoria, Oregon.
- Statement on Forest Resources, May 10, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1134)
- Law Day Dinner - Oregon City, Oregon, May 11, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1135)
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Oregon, May 11, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1136)
  Luncheon - Rockefeller for President Committee, Beaverton Elks Club.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Oregon, May 12, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1137)
  Coos Bay Rotary Club luncheon - Coos Bay, Oregon.
- Primary Campaign 1964 - Oregon, May 12, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1138)
  Statement on Outdoor Recreation - Portland, Oregon
- Primary Campaign 1964 - California, May 13, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1139)
  Humboldt State College - Arcata, California.
- Primary Campaign 1964 - Portland, Oregon, May 13, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1140)
  University of Portland.
- McMinnville Chamber of Commerce- McMinnville, Oregon, May 14, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1141)
- NAR Statement re: Oregon Primary, May 16, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1142)
- World's Fair 1964 - New York City, May 18, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1143)
  Michigan Day at World's Fair - luncheon sponsored by Economic Club of Detroit, Michigan
- San Fernando Valley State College - Northridge, California, May 19, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1144)
- 1964 Primary Campaign - North Hollywood, California, May 19, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1145)
  Statewide TV program.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Riverside, California, May 20, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1146)
  California Baptist College.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - San Bernadino, California, May 20, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1147)
  Luncheon - San Bernadino Service Clubs.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Foreign Policy Statement (Southeast Asia), May 21, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1148)
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Stockton, California, May 21, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1149)
  University of the Pacific.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - San Francisco, California, May 22, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1150)
  Breakfast and speech at the Bay Area Republican Alliance.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - San Francisco, California, May 22, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1151)
  Luncheon with labor leaders; remarks on health care for the aged.
- Primary Campaign 1964 - California, May 25, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1152)
  Statement re: Eisenhower Statement - San Diego, California.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - San Diego, California, May 25, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1153)
  San Diego State College.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Los Angeles, California, May 25, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1154)
  Dinner with Southern California Campaign Workers.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Santa Barbara, California, May 26, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1155)
  Luncheon at Channel City Club.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Burbank, California, May 27, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1156)
  Luncheon - Los Angeles County Women's Committee.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Monterey, California, May 28, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1157)
  Luncheon - NAR for President Committee.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - Los Angeles, California, May 28, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1158)
  Statewide TV Program, KTLA.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - San Francisco, California, May 29, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1159)
  Luncheon - Commonwealth Club of California.
- 1964 Primary Campaign - California, June 1, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1160)
  Campaign Closing Statements.
- Statement: California Primary Results, June 2-3, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1161)
- Suffolk County Republican Committee - Huntington, Long Island, New York, June 4, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1162)
- Governors' Conference - Cleveland, Ohio, June 7, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1163)
- New York Delegation to 1964 Republican National Convention - Albany, New York, June 11, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1164)
- NAR Statements re: GOP Nomination for President, June 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1165)
- United Jewish Appeal - Person-to-Person Telephone Program - New York City, June 25, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1166)
- Long Beach Republican Committee - Joseph F. Carlino Scholarship Fund Dinner - Long Beach, New York, June 25, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1167)
- Saratoga Springs State Park - Groundbreaking Ceremonies for Saratoga Performing Arts Center - Saratoga Springs, New York, June 30, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1168)
- Scranton Show - CBS, June 28, 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1169)
- Republican National Convention - San Francisco, California, July 6, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1170)
- Republican Platform Committee Hearings, July 7, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1171)
- Statement re: Inadequacy of Draft Platform, July 12, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1172)
- Nominating and Seconding Speeches for NAR, July 11, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1173)
- Miscellaneous Statements, Interviews re: Republican National Convention, July 12, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1174)
- Civil Rights Rally - San Francisco, California, July 12, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1175)
- Republican National Convention - Planning and Arrangements - San Francisco, California, July 13-17, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1176)
- Statement re: Extremism Amendment to Platform, July 14, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1177)
- Statement re: Barry Goldwater's Acceptance Speech, July 17, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1178)
- Syracuse University - Syracuse, New York, August 4, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1179)
  Dedication Dinner for Samuel I. Newhouse Communications Center.
- Chief Justices of the United States - New York City, August 5, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1180)
- GOP County Chairmen and Vice Chairmen Meeting - Albany, New York, August 6, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1181)
- American Bar Association - New York City, August 10, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1182)
- Republican Meeting - Hershey, Pennsylvania, August 12, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1183)
  Includes NAR's notes on extremism and Republican unity.
- Federation of Women's Republican Clubs of New York State - Niagara Falls, New York, August 21, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1184)
- New York Republican State Committee - New York City, August 31, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1185)
- Not Used (Box 29, Folder 1186)
- County Officers Association - Kiamesha Lake, New York, September 21, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1187)
- Associated Industries of New York State - Whiteface, New York, September 25, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1188)
- 1964 Campaign - Republican Committees - Albany, New York, September 25, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1189)
  NAR introduces Senator Barry Goldwater at the State Office Building.
- Steuben Day Parade - New York City, September 26, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1190)
- National Legislative Leaders - Executive Committee - New York City, September 26, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1191)
- Syracuse Chamber of Commerce and Central New York Trade Association - Syracuse, New York, September 30, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1192)
- Pulaski Memorial Committee - Pulaski Day Parade - New York City, October 4, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1193)
- Brooklyn Navy Yard Workers Rally - New York City, October 4, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1194)
  NAR's appearance was cancelled.
- 1964 Campaign - Republican Committees - New York City, October 7, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1195)
  Reception for John V. Lindsay.
- Women's Westchester Republican Club - Eastchester, New York, October 8, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1196)
- Division of Housing and Community Renewal - New York City, October 9, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1197)
- American Public Health Association - New York City, October 9, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1198)
- Columbus Citizens Committee - Columbus Day Parade - New York City, October 12, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1198A)
- Airport Operators Council, Inc. - New York City, October 14, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1199)
- Alfred E. Smith Memorial Foundation, Inc. - Annual Dinner - New York City, October 14, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1200)
- Governor's Committee on the Education and Employment of Women, October 15, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1201)
- Urban League of Greater New York - New York City, October 15, 1964 (Box 29, Folder 1202)
- 1964 Campaign - Republican Committees - Schenectady, New York, October 20, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1203)
  Luncheon rally, Oneonta Elks Club; reception, Cobleskill; dinner, County Republican Leaders, Schenectady; campaign rally, Hellenic Center.
- State University of New York - Jamestown, October 23, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1204)
  Dinner - Alumni Association of State University, College of Fredonia.
- Grand Council of Columbia Association in Civil Service - New York City, October 24, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1205)
- 1964 Campaign - Republican County Committees, October 26, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1206)
  Dinner - Albany County Republican Committee for Senator Keating - Albany, New York Rally - Rensselaer County Republican Committee - Troy, New York
- Young Republicans of Warren County - Glen Falls, New York, October 29, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1207)
- New York State Traffic Safety Council - Luncheon of Finance and Advisory Committee - New York City, November 16, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1208)
- Building Industry Employers Association of New York State - New York City, November 16, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1209)
- Board of Directors of Commerce and Industry Association - New York City, November 17, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1210)
- National Council of Chief State School Officers - New York City, November 18, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1211)
- Federal Union, Inc. - 25th Anniversary Banquet - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, November 20, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1212)
  NAR receives "Union Pioneer Award" at Congress Hall.
- Federal Union, Inc. - 25th Anniversary Banquet - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, November 20, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1212A)
  Drafts of speech (including drafts by Henry Kissinger).
- Verrazano-Narrows Bridge - Opening Ceremonies - Staten Island, New York, November 21, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1213)
- Department of Mental Hygiene - Staten Island, New York, December 2, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1214)
  Groundbreaking ceremony for the Institute for Basic Research in Mental Retardation.
- Republican Governors' Association - Denver, Colorado, December 4, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1215)
- Office for Regional Development, Mid-Hudson Valley Region - New Paltz, New York, December 5, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1216)
  Alexander Aldrich attended on behalf of NAR.
- Rome and Utica Chamber of Commerce - Utica, New York, December 10, 1964 (Box 30, Folder 1217)
- Annual Message to the Legislature - Albany, New York, January 6, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 1218)
- Annual Message to the Legislature - Albany, New York, January 6, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 1218A)
- New York State Women's Joint Legislative Forum - Albany, New York, January 12, 1965 (Box 30, Folder 1219)
- New York State Agricultural Society - Annual Dinner - Albany, New York, January 13, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1220)
- Chamber of Commerce - Erie, Niagara and Wyoming Counties - Buffalo, New York, January 14, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1221)
  Luncheon, speaks, R.
- Cattaraugus and Chautauqua Counties Chamber of Commerce - Jamestown, New York, January 14, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1222)
- New York State Science and Technology Foundation - Luncheon for Board of Directors - New York City, January 15, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1223)
- Eloy Alfero International Foundation Republic of Panama - New York City, January 15, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1224)
  Presentation by Lt. Gov. Wilson of the Grand Cross & Citation to Thomas Hollywood.
- New York State Association for Mental Health - Albany, New York, January 19, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1225)
- Kiwanis Club - Albany, New York, January 19, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1226)
  Luncheon for the Golden Anniversary of the Albany Kiwanis Club.
- Association of County Highway Superintendents - Albany, New York, January 21, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1227)
- New York Academy of Medicine - Memorial for Dr. Paul H. Hoch - New York City, January 21, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1228)
- Westchester County Republican Committee - New York City, January 21, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1229)
- Alfalfa Club - Washington, DC, January 23, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1230)
- New York Academy of Osteopathy - New York City, January 23, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1231)
  NAR receives Medallion of Honor, Foundation for Research.
- Women's National Republican Club - New York City, January 30, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1232)
- New York State Department of Public Works - Albany, New York, February 2, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1233)
  Luncheon, receive award, Parade Magazine.
- Empire State Chamber of Commerce - Albany, New York, February 2, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1234)
- Office for Regional Development - Rochester, New York, February 4, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1234A)
  Luncheon, Rochester, Monroe, Yates, Orleans, Genesee, Livingston, Ontario, Seneca & Wayne Chambers of Commerce.
- Boy Scouts, Region 2 - Albany, New York, February 8, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1235)
- Federation of Women's of New York State Republican Clubs - Albany, New York, February 8, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1236)
- Association of Towns of the State of New York - New York City, February 9, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1237)
- Association of the Fire Districts of New York State - New York City, February 9, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1238)
- Veterans Hospital - Bath, New York, February 11, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1239)
- State University of New York, College at Alfred, February 11, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1240)
- Hornell Chamber of Commerce - Hornell, New York, February 11, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1241)
- American Legion - Annual Legislative Dinner - Albany, New York, February 16, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1242)
- American Jewish Congress - Annual Legislative Dinner - Albany, New York, February 16, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1243)
- Saratoga County Republican Committee Dinner, February 18, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1244)
- House Public Works Committee - Water Pollution Control - Washington, DC, February 23, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1245)
- New York State Business and Professional Women's Club - Conference - Albany, New York, February 23, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1246)
- Delaware River Basin Authority - Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, February 24, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1247)
- New York State Council of Churches - Albany, New York, March 1, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1248)
  Meet with Legislative Seminar.
- League of Women Voters - Legislative Conference - Albany, New York, March 1, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1249)
- Association of Broadcasters - Legislative Dinner - Albany, New York, March 2, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1250)
- Regional Tour, March 4, 1965 (Box 31, Folder 1251)
  Office for Regional Development - Luncheon, Souther-Tier-East Finger Lakes Region, Broome, Tioga, Ostego, Delaware, Chenango, Tompkins, Cortland - Binghamton, New York. Visit Binghamton State hospital, Kirkwood Industrial Park, Republican Leaders Meeting, WNBF-TV Show, Binghamton Press & Sun.
- National Wildlife Federation - Washington, DC, March 5, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1252)
- New York Young Republican Club - New York City, March 5, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1253)
- Inner Circle - Dinner - New York City, March 6, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1254)
- United Parents Association - Albany, New York, March 8, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1255)
- New York State Department of Commerce - Women's Council - Albany, New York, March 8, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1256)
- American Institute for Free Labor Development - Washington, DC, March 10, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1257)
  Graduating exercise.
- Civil Service Employees Association - Annual Dinner - Albany, New York, March 11, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1258)
- New York State Publishers Association - Annual Dinner - Albany, New York, March 15, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1259)
- St. Patrick's Day Parade and Celebration Committee - New York City, March 17, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1260)
  Review parade, attend dinner - Society of Friendly Sons of St. Patrick.
- United Jewish Appeal - New York City, March 18, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1261)
- Legislative Correspondents Association - Albany, New York, March 18, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1262)
- National Association for the Advancement of Colored People - New York State Chapter - Annual Convention - Albany, New York, March 23, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1263)
- County Officers Association - Kiamesha Lake, New York - Cancelled., March 30, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1264)
- Office for Regional Development - Watertown, New York, April 1, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1265)
  Luncheon - Greater Watertown Chamber of Commerce.
- Office for Regional Development - Massena, New York, April 1, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1266)
  Dinner meeting - Massena Chamber of Commerce.
- Port Authority Trans-Hudson (PATH) - New York City and Jersey City, April 8, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1267)
  Luncheon and inauguration of new cars. Dr. Ronan for NAR.
- World's Fair 1964 - 2nd Year Opening - New York City, April 21, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1268)
- World's Fair 1964 - Opening of New York State Pavilion - New York City, April 22, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1269)
- American National Theatre and Academy - New York City, April 26, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1270)
- Cornell University - Charter Convocation - Ithaca, New York, April 27, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1271)
- Kingston Lions Club - Opening Ceremonies - Kingston, New York, April 27, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1272)
- Interstate Commerce Commission - Testimony on Passenger Train Service - New York City, April 28, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1273)
- Mount Sinai School of Medicine - New York City, April 28, 1965 (Box 32, Folder 1274)
- State University of New York, Delhi - Dedication of Agricultural and Technical College - Delhi, New York, May 1, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 1275)
- Governor's Conference on the Aging - New York City, May 7, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 1276)
- Great Lakes Basin Pollution Conference - Cleveland, Ohio, May 10, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 1277)
- American Society for Public Administration, Albany Chapter - Albany, New York, May 11, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 1278)
- State University of New York - New York City, May 13, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 1279)
  Inauguration ceremonies for Dr. Samuel B. Gould as president.
- Association of New York State Young Republican Clubs - Livingston Manor, New York, May 15, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 1280)
- Youth Opportunity Centers - Dedication Ceremonies - Albany-Schenectady-Troy area, New York, May 18, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 1281)
- New York State Civil Defense Commission - Women's Civil Defense Council Lunch - Albany, New York, May 18, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 1282)
- Senate Special Subcommittee on Air and Water Pollution - Testimony - Washington, DC, May 19, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 1283)
- World's Fair 1964 - New York City, May 20, 1965 (Box 33, Folder 1284)
  New York State Council on the Arts - review art exhibit; Reception for the Society of Foreign Consuls in New York.